(Penny:)My point is, I know more
about dating than you,
(Penny:)and if you were as smart
as you think you are,
(Penny:)you would listen to me.
(Sheldon:)If you know so much,
how come I have a date tonight
(Sheldon:)and you have nothing better
to do than drive me to it?
(Penny:)Fair point.
(Penny:)You know,
there's something
(Raj:)I've always wondered
about Aquaman.
(Leonard:)Yeah?
Where does he poop?
(Penny:)What?
(Raj:)What would a toilet
look like in Atlantis?
(Raj:)How would you flush it?
(Raj:)And when you did flush it,
where would the poop go?
(Leonard(phone rings):)Hold that thought.
(Leonard(phone rings):)Hey, Howard.
What's going on?
(Penny(arriving):)What...
(Leonard(phone rings):)Hold on.
Howard, Howard, slow down.
(Scene:)The robot hand
is stuck on your what?
(Leonard(phone rings):)You're not going
to believe this.